<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<LanguageData>

    <JDG_AmbitionAcquired>{0} has been overwhelmed with fervor!</JDG_AmbitionAcquired>
    <!-- 0 is the label of the HediffDef associated with the mental break. -->
    <JDG_AmbitionDetails>{PAWN_pronoun} is {0} and must satisfy this ambition or face consequences!</JDG_AmbitionDetails>
    <JDG_AmbitionFailed>An ambition was failed</JDG_AmbitionFailed>
    <JDG_AmbitionSucceeded>An ambition was completed</JDG_AmbitionSucceeded>
    <JDG_InspirationFailed>An inspiration was failed</JDG_InspirationFailed>
    <JDG_InspirationSucceeded>An inspiration was completed</JDG_InspirationSucceeded>

    <!-- Elements relating to specific ambitions. Some do not have a fail and/or success message because they are handled by mental states or other letters. -->
    <JDG_AmbitionFailed_Adamant>{0} was unable to remain in full control of {PAWN_possessive} emotions and succumbed to another roiling wave of fervor - leaving {PAWN_objective} torn and adrift. {PAWN_possessive} confidence is shaken and will need time to recover.</JDG_AmbitionFailed_Adamant>
    <JDG_AmbitionSucceeded_Adamant>{0} was able to remain in control of {PAWN_possessive} emotions. {PAWN_pronoun} is feeling more confident and capable.</JDG_AmbitionSucceeded_Adamant>
    <JDG_AmbitionSucceeded_MeldIntoShadow>{0} remained true to {PAWN_possessive} goal by leveraging strength found in shadow. {PAWN_pronoun} is feeling emboldened to hasten the spread of darkness over this benighted world.</JDG_AmbitionSucceeded_MeldIntoShadow>
    <JDG_AmbitionSucceeded_DepressiveFixation>{0} plunged through the depths of despair and found truth - at least, according to {PAWN_objective}. {PAWN_pronoun} is viewing the world differently and with greater determination.</JDG_AmbitionSucceeded_DepressiveFixation>
    <JDG_AmbitionSucceeded_RecruitmentMotivation>{0} lured a soul from the agonizing brightness into the pure, blissful darkness - {PAWN_pronoun} loathes the idiom about "bringing into the light" - and is feeling rather proud of themselves. {PAWN_pronoun} is likely to be more confident in conversation for a time, or perhaps just more annoyingly talkative.</JDG_AmbitionSucceeded_RecruitmentMotivation>
    <JDG_AmbitionSucceeded_Bloodletter>{0} is content with the amount of violence committed. {PAWN_pronoun} is feeling ready for more ambitious battles.</JDG_AmbitionSucceeded_Bloodletter>
    <JDG_AmbitionSucceeded_CleansingFury>{0} revelled in the slaughter as heretics were purged of their sins through death. {PAWN_pronoun} is excited to continue cleansing this benighted world of its heresies.</JDG_AmbitionSucceeded_CleansingFury>
    <JDG_AmbitionSucceeded_ContemplatingMurder>{0} is a murderer. {PAWN_pronoun} does not seem bothered by this. In fact, {PAWN_pronoun} is eerily stoic and calm. {PAWN_possessive} gaze is steely and promises death to all.</JDG_AmbitionSucceeded_ContemplatingMurder>
    <JDG_AmbitionSucceeded_EndureSuffering>{0} has withstood the trial of suffering and emerged intact. {PAWN_pronoun} is unfazed by the trials that lie ahead, and is determined to face them with stubborn resilience.</JDG_AmbitionSucceeded_EndureSuffering>
    <JDG_AmbitionFailed_CravingInspiration>{0} was unable to find something to atone for - leaving {PAWN_objective} bereft of a justified cause to seek repentance. {PAWN_possessive} is left shaken by the idea that {PAWN_pronoun} is guilty without knowing why, and will not be able to shrug off this diffidence for a long time.</JDG_AmbitionFailed_CravingInspiration>
    <JDG_AmbitionSucceeded_CravingInspiration>{0} found something to atone for, and is eager to absolve themselves of their sin. {PAWN_pronoun} is guilty and is - strangely enough - proud of this fact.</JDG_AmbitionSucceeded_CravingInspiration>

    <!-- Elements relating to specific inspirations. Some do not have a fail and/or success message because they are handled by mental states or other letters. -->
    <JDG_InspirationSucceeded_InduceWithdrawal>{0} has suffered the agony of withdrawal for long enough that {PAWN_pronoun} feels like the sin of joy has been purged.</JDG_InspirationSucceeded_InduceWithdrawal>
    <JDG_InspirationSucceeded_Kinslayer>{0} has sacrificed {PAWN_possessive} kin. The joy {PAWN_pronoun} once felt has been supplanted by a mixture of horror, guilt, and awe. The Dark God approves of all three.</JDG_InspirationSucceeded_Kinslayer>
    <JDG_InspirationSucceeded_Bondbreaker>{0} has sacrificed someone important to {PAWN_possessive}. Having ripped a soul so precious out of its body for {PAWN_pronoun} deity, {PAWN_pronoun} feels... better. {PAWN_pronoun} feels more free. {PAWN_pronoun} feels closer to the Dark God. Joy, happiness, companionship... such petty things were holding {0} back. But can {PAWN_pronoun} truly live without any such relationships at all?</JDG_InspirationSucceeded_Bondbreaker>
    <JDG_InspirationSucceeded_VowOfSilence>{0} has remained silent for a full year, and has decided that enough is enough - one cannot silence the world while remaining silent. {PAWN_pronoun} is ready once again to offer up screaming sacrifices to the Dark God.</JDG_InspirationSucceeded_VowOfSilence>
    <JDG_InspirationSucceeded_EmbraceScarcity>{0} has experienced what scarcity truly feels like, and finds comfort in this. {PAWN_pronoun} is certain that this world, while disgustingly abundant, may yet still be saved and so {PAWN_possessive} work must continue.</JDG_InspirationSucceeded_EmbraceScarcity>
    <!-- This version of failure only occurs if leaving the colony is impossible (IE. because the justiciar is downed or somewhere where leaving is not allowed.)-->
    <JDG_InspirationFailed_EmbraceScarcity>{0} could not truly feel the embrace of scarcity in this accursed world. {PAWN_pronoun} chose to do the one thing that could guarantee {PAWN_possessive} liberation from it - to take {PAWN_possessive} own life.</JDG_InspirationFailed_EmbraceScarcity>
    <JDG_InspirationSucceeded_BurnInlight>{0} endured the horrid light and persevered. {PAWN_pronoun} is certain that an apocalyptic event in which the entire world is engulfed in endless light cannot come to pass as long as {PAWN_pronoun} remains strong.</JDG_InspirationSucceeded_BurnInlight>
    <JDG_InspirationFailed_BurnInlight>{0} could not endure the horrid light. {PAWN_pronoun} is convinced that when the great veil of shadow descends and cleanses this world, {PAWN_pronoun} might be found unworthy of salvation from the light that {PAWN_pronoun} failed to challenge. This has left {PAWN_objective} terrified that {PAWN_pronoun} has learned the wrong skills and must find a new path.</JDG_InspirationFailed_BurnInlight>
    <JDG_InspirationSucceeded_SeekRepentance>{0} has found {PAWN_possessive} trials and overcome them. {PAWN_pronoun} is feeling like a right and proper servant of the Dark God once again - tested and triumphant.</JDG_InspirationSucceeded_SeekRepentance>
    <!-- This version of failure only occurs if leaving the colony is impossible (IE. because the justiciar is downed or somewhere where leaving is not allowed.)-->
    <JDG_InspirationFailed_SeekRepentance>{0} could not find and overcome the trials that the Dark God had prepared for {PAWN_possessive} and is crushed by the failure. {PAWN_pronoun} knows exactly how to repent of this failure and to find a path toward redemption... but it cannot be done in this life. The Dark God beckons, and {0} obeys.</JDG_InspirationFailed_SeekRepentance>
    <!-- There is no success letter for Commune with Darkness, as the Inspiration ceases to exist on death. -->
    <JDG_InspirationFailed_CommuneWithDarkness>{0} did not answer the Dark God's summons on {PAWN_possessive} own terms. The Dark God beckons, though, and will not be denied.</JDG_InspirationFailed_CommuneWithDarkness>

    <!-- Elements relating to acolytes and their journey to becoming justiciars. -->
    <JDG_AcolyteWhispers>{0} hears whispers</JDG_AcolyteWhispers>
    <JDG_AcolyteWhispersDesc>{0} can hear an alluring voice calling out to them. It whispers of the beauty and sanctity of the dark. It whispers of a path of pain and suffering - and of salvation.\n\nIt whispers of a chosen place in the ranks of the justiciars. Will {0} open {PAWN_possessive} heart to these ideals, or will {PAWN_pronoun} shrug it off? The voice will return if rejected, but it may whisper to another and may take a long time to choose again.</JDG_AcolyteWhispersDesc>
    <JDG_AcolyteRecruited>{0} has become an acolyte!</JDG_AcolyteRecruited>
    <JDG_AcolyteRecruitedDesc>{0} has been inducted into the faith as an acolyte. Experiencing pain and nurturing favor over time - or violently killing fellow acolytes or even justiciars and seizing their power - will assure {PAWN_possessive} ascent to the coveted title of justiciar.</JDG_AcolyteRecruitedDesc>
    <JDG_AcolyteChosen>{0} has been chosen!</JDG_AcolyteChosen>
    <JDG_AcolyteChosenDesc>Through {PAWN_possessive} deeds in the name of the Dark God, {0} has been chosen to join the ranks of the justiciars! {PAWN_pronoun} must now take the oaths and select the path to the embrace of the void they will walk. This decision can be delayed, but it can only be made once.</JDG_AcolyteChosenDesc>
    <JDG_AcolyteExpelled>{0} has failed as an acolyte!</JDG_AcolyteExpelled>
    <JDG_AcolyteExpelledDesc>{0} failed in {PAWN_possessive} duties as an acolyte and could not find the path to the Dark God's favor. {PAWN_pronoun} has been stripped of {PAWN_possessive} station and cast out into the ranks of the heretics.</JDG_AcolyteExpelledDesc>

</LanguageData>